A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Pamphlet File, Series 2 FA264
Rockefeller Archive Center
- U.S. Congress, 87th, Senate and House of Representatives, 1961 June 30 (Box 37, Folder 411)
- U.S. Congress, 88th, House of Representatives, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 412)
- U.S. Congress, 90th, House of Representatives, 1967 September 27 (Box 37, Folder 413)
- U.S. Congress, 90th, Senate, 1964 October 26 (Box 37, Folder 414)
- U.S. Congress, 91st, Senate, 1969 July 9 (Box 37, Folder 415)
- U.S. Court of Claims, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 416)
- U.S. Dept. of State. Bureau of Public Affairs, 1973 May 14 (Box 37, Folder 417)
- U.S. Dept. of the Interior. National Park Service, 1939-1966 (Box 37, Folder 418)
- U.S. Dept. of the Interior. National Park Service, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 419)
- Uhl, Raymond, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 420)
- Uttar Pradesh, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 421)
- Va-Vd, 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 422)
- Ve-Vh, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 423)
- Vergara, B. S., 1969 December (Box 38, Folder 424)
- Vi-Vz, undated (Box 38, Folder 425)
- Vincent, George E., 1918-1930 (Box 38, Folder 426)
- Virginia Conservation Commission, 1940-1943 (Box 38, Folder 427)
- Wa-Wd, 1933-1974 (Box 38, Folder 428)
- Wackerman, A. E., 1945 June (Box 38, Folder 429)
- Wakefield, Dan, 1968 March (Box 38, Folder 430)
- Washburn, A. Michael, 1967 September (Box 38, Folder 431)
- Washington Irving, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 432)
- Waynesboro High School Faculty, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 433)
- Weaver, Warren, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 434)
- Weir, John M., 1952-1965 (Box 39, Folder 435)
- Welch, William Henry, 1920 November 5 (Box 39, Folder 436)
- Welsch, Delane E., 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 437)
- We-Wh, 1960-1980; 1960-1967 (Box 39, Folder 438)
- White, Franc, 1975 June (Box 39, Folder 439)
- Wi-Wn, 1937-1972 (Box 39, Folder 440)
- "Wild Viruses" by Greer Williams, 1967-1970 (Box 40, Folder 441)
- Williams, Greer, 1964-1976 (Box 40, Folder 442)
- Willner, Ann Ruth, 1966 September 30 (Box 40, Folder 443)
- Wo-Wz, 1957-1970 (Box 40, Folder 444)
- Wolfenstein, E. Victor, 1965 October 30 (Box 40, Folder 445)
- Works, George A., 1943 December (Box 40, Folder 446)
- Wortman, Sterling, 1964-1973 (Box 40, Folder 447)
- Wyatt, Bernard L., 1921 (Box 41, Folder 448)
- Ya-Yn, 1970 September (Box 41, Folder 449)
- Yo-Yz, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 450)
- Young, Oran R., 1966 January 1 (Box 41, Folder 451)